Ohm... thump-thump, thump-thump.
Heavy stone, solid within.
My skull is forged in steel
Against diamond blades,
spears, wooden arrows, and firelocks.
By the power of merit,
Magic,
and the essence of a hundred and eight roots.
Descend and dwell within my body.
[Chanting]
From now on.You shall be invulnerable.
No blade can cut you, no bullet can pierce you.
Singha.
Mom.
There’s so much you haven't told me, Mom.
There!
What the hell?
What are you spacing out for?
Your mind's already drifted off to the Gulf by now.
Tons of work to do in the shop.
The food’s still not cooked.
When is it going to be ready?
I’m just worried that
Singha won’t come to open the shop
So that’s what you were on about.
Don’t worry. Singha’s gonna show up anyway.
He loves this shop to death.
You should worry about yourself instead.
You're so distracted that
no work is getting done.
And... aren't you even a bit
curious about where Auntie and Sing went?
No.
Don't want to know. Not my business.
Ok.
But I'm telling you,
Singha wouldn't leave us behind.
And neither would Mae Pim.
Think about it.
Without Mae Pim and Singha.
Would you and I even be
standing here, complaining like this? Huh?
Think about it!
Woah, you asshole!
only had one tiny doubt.
Way to make me feel guilty for life.
-Unbelievable.
-No more doubts, okay?
Understand? Just get the damn job done.
You.
-Just do your job right.
-Whoa!
A new bar just opened up?
Who is it now?
Uh.
We just opened.
Can I get a bottle of beer? You selling yet?
Yep, we're selling.
Small bottles only.
Help yourself at the fridge.
First one's 80 baht.
That fridge over there. That one!
Whoa.
Look at your face. So fake.
What? Don't be a nosy prick.
It's my life.
Is it just the two of you running the place?
Oh, no.
It's a partnership between three of us.
Here, the owner.
And my friends are partners.
And this one? She's the servant.
You asshole!
You on vacation, or just here solo?
Oh,
I'm working over at the Amarin Center Hotel.
But the manager...
Accused me of being a smart-ass,
so I just quit.
That's good.
Now that you've been kicked out,
What’s your next move?
Got another hotel lined up?
No chance.
By now, they’ve probably sent
warning letters to every hotel in town.
-Poor soul.
-You freaking flirt.
Hey.
So.
Are there any job openings here?
What can you do?
Anything you need.
Kitchen, dishes, tables,
DJing, opening up the shop.
I can try.
You're in.
Done. Get to it.
You.
Go help Mom at the other shop.
You don't need to come here anymore.
I'll stay here with her, just the two of us.
She seems capable. Perfect.
Oh, by the way.
-what's your name?
-I'm Toon.
Toon? Wow, that rhymes with my name!
-ToonJoe, ToonJoe.
-This asshole right here is a total creep.
And I'm...
Foon.
JoeToon, JoeToon, Wow.
Hey, You.
Haven't finished sweeping,
and you're already drinking?
You’re gonna get drunk
and won't be able to sweep.
Ooh, look at you, making that face!
Ugh, picking on me again?
Classic you.
This spot is absolutely beautiful.
Thinking of setting up
a dock for international imports.
Those things over there
won't be a problem, right?
That trash pile?
One sweep and it's gone.
Headman Tia’s property.
He's been a thorn in my side.
Next week, an MP is coming down
from Bangkok.
To scout the location and see
about partnering up for the pier.
Everything needs to be kept in order.
These politicians...
They're just greedy bastards.
Right?
Anyway, if you can't talk sense
into them, hand them over to me.
These assholes deserve to die with honor.
Why is it so dark?
Where did everyone go?
Hey.
Hey, where did everyone go?
Surprise!
Whoa, look at that! Completely stunned.
Take a good look!
How do you like that? Look at it!
Our work is no joke, you know.
Yeah.
Wow.
-You guys are fucking good.
- Yeah, I hear that all the time.
Are you seriously tearing up right now?
It's touching.
Asshole.
Man, it's our blood, sweat, and tears.
We were nothing but outcasts.
Always the underdogs.
Who would've thought?
That we could actually build a place like this.
Holy shit!
So fucking awesome!
-Well, what are you waiting for? Bring it in!
-Hell yeah!
-You bastard.
-Fucking awesome.
-Hey, Joe.
-Huh?
Is that your girl?
Hell no!
That's Toon.
She just applied for the job today.
You were out, and we had
a spot open. I hired her to help us out.
Yes.
I'm Singha Immortal.
Welcome.
Oh, yeah!
Celebration time!
I'll take you guys out for a treat.
Hey.
Joe.
Damn, he’s already passed out.
Singha.
You’ve been gone for so long.
How’d you get so fit?
What have you been doing?
You like it?
I'm just saying you look good, that's all...
Yep.
Look good.
I know you like it.
Even while I'm asleep,
I can tell how much of a flirt you are.
Joe.
Not true.
Thanks for nudging me.
Damn, you guys get drunk
and talking like this.
Look at how he talks to me.
You should just get drunk and pass out.
Oh, thanks for nudging me twice.
Inspector.
I've found the target now. Name is Singha.
Inside the shop.
Just keep an eye on him.
Be careful.
Copy that.
What are you doing?
Nothing.
Or you.
Toon.
You.
Foon, you okay?
No need to fear being drunk.
Because we're heavyweight drinker.
The face is red only because shy
and embarrassed.
You guys are so cool.
Seem to really love each other.
We grew up together.
Joe and Foon are just kids
from around Walking Street.
Foon's stepfather tried to rape her.
So he ran away from home.
And Joe.
His dad would get drunk
and beat the hell out of him.
Great lives they had, right? Real quality stuff.
So, we stick together. Better off this way.
Are you okay?
Me?
I have nothing. I'm just...
A piece of shit. Naturally born like this.
How are you a piece of shit?
Forget it.
Living in a shitty city like this.
Being a good person is hard.
But I'm done with all that shit now.
Let's see what happens.
Maybe this shitty city
will become a little less shitty.
Hey, the road is plenty wide!
What's the rush, your dad's funeral? Asshole.
Jackass.
Two bikes, just for show.
If I had one, I'd ride seven at once.
Such a shame.
I can't ride a bike.
Asshole.
Never taken a bus in my life.
Fuck it. That was deep.
-Damn!
-Damn it!
Screw you.
Run away!
You’re a traitor.
Hey, what's up?
What the hell is going on?
There's nothing left.
Who the fuck did this? Motherfucker!
If I ever find out who it was.
I'll fucking kill them all.
Fuck!
You son of a bitch!
It's been taken care of, boss.
There won't be
any trouble from this Village Chief, right?
Yes, sir.
Probably won't use
The rubber plantation as a graveyard.
I said I'm not selling!
What part of no don't you get?
Go tell your boss
to stay the hell away from me!
I'm being respectful to you, sir.
Why do you have to be
so aggressive with me?
So, you're not selling.
I said I won't sell!
Get out! Now!
The rubber isn't even selling well.
How pitiful.
But he just won't listen. Stubborn as hell.
Yes, Mr. Vinit.
Everything is settled, sir.
No need to call me yourself. I feel bad.
Yes, you can come.
Oh, please come, sir.
It won't be dull, sir.
Definitely not a dull moment.
I'll have people ready for you.
I guarantee there will be
plenty of people giving you flowers.
Yes, sir. I'll take care of it. Goodbye, sir.
Go.
Dammit!
Always demanding shit
but never spends a goddamn penny.
Damn you, Vinit.
This has happened way too many times now.
You...
You're a real piece of work, you know that?
Aren't you afraid of karma at all?
Oh, please!
Why should I be afraid?
Who knows if heaven and hell even exist.
It's about the present moment.
Money, power.
I need it all.
Impressive.
Just the kind of person
the world needs right now.
Why?
Is someone like me really that important?
Of course you are.
So we can tell the difference between
what a piece of shit looks like,
what a good person looks like,
and what someone...
in the middle looks like.
As for you, you'd be called...
Pure evil.
Greedy.
But understandable.
Get a boat ready for me.
Fuck.
It's over. Immortal Bar.
I think this is just the beginning.
It’s a total wreck.
You really think you can start over?
Immortal this bar was the dream.
This is our life.
It's our soul.
Are we really gonna let it just end like this.
I've got goosebumps listening to you.
I'm okay with that.
Shit.
That's dope.
Not giving up, and you're still fucking fighting.
Oh.
I don't even know where the fuck to start.
Hey, at least the jukebox still works.
We have music.
We got booze.
We got glasses.
and we got a servant.
So, open the damn bar!
What the hell are we waiting for?
-Who are you calling a servant, asshole?
-You, of course! Forgot your roots already?
Fuck off! Just grab the chairs and get moving.
I'm cutting your salary in half!
Hey.
Where the fuck is your glass, Joe?
I don't drink while I'm working, asshole.
Cheers!
Cheers! Now go call the insurance.
Goddammit.
I wasted so much cash
on the decor for nothing.
In this shitty condition,
and the place is somehow packed!
-if people wanna come, they'll come. Who know?
-Yeah.
Aren't you scared they'll come back?
Fear what?
We don't even know who the fuck did this.
Hey.
You're no angel.
Heard people are
already lining up to get you.
It just hit me.
If we wanna find out
who's behind this, we gotta lure them here.
-Huh?
-What?
How?
Shit.
What’s up, Pattaya people!
To whoever trashed my place
last night and thought I couldn't reopen
So sorry, man. We're back in business!
Big thanks to the guys who wrecked
the bar for giving me a new concept.
Don't forget.
I'm right here waiting for you.
Immortal
Come by anytime.
Immortal.
Cheer! Cheer!
Did you find the person with the Wind Spirit?
For your protection.
Invincibility is not eternal.
I command you to do good deeds.
The day you commit evil.
Your amulets.
Will lose their power over time.
Yet, there exists one
whose power remains eternal.
The one who
unites the four elemental
spirits Earth, Water, Air, and Fire.
In one soul.
That person shall be truly immortal.
No soul shall ever bring them down.
May this campaign into battle,
may you be victorious,
and protect our kingdom.
It can't help but revealing their true self.
It just can't.
This karma has been with him
since birth, just like his father.
It told me once that
his son has a soul of wind.
The stronger the wind blows against him,
the more he gains the power of a storm.
His emotions follow the same rule.
So, what's it like?
Is it a good thing or a bad thing?
When you possess great power.
But lose control at a crossroads.
It's always gonna lead you down a dark path.
Take a good look at it.
His life has been nothing
but one disaster after another.
So, what should we do? Can it be fixed?
Pim.
I can't fix anyone's karma.
Hey, you guys.
I kicked you out, but
you won't leave. Unbelievable.
Who the fuck are you?
Oh, I see.
You bastard.
It was you guys, right?
Who burned down my bar!
Let my friend go right fucking now,
you bastard!
Who the hell are you to order me around?
Huh? You're just a junkie.
-You calling us junkies?
-Damn, right.
Go tell Arnon.
I'm not going anywhere. This is my bar!
Then maybe we'll just burn it down again.
Hey, let's go!
You gonna burn it? Huh?
-Hey.
-Singha.
Hey! Let's get out of here.
Move it! Let’s go!
Joe.
-Joe.
-Foon, go check on Singha.
Singha.
-Singha. Singha.
-Are you okay?
-Take it slow.
-Singha got shot!
Hey.
-Singha.
Singha.
-Stay with me! Don't you die on me.
-Singha.
Singha, wake up!
Toon, Joe.
Help me carry Singha!
I’m taking Singh to the hospital. Hurry up!
-Hurry up!
-Hey.
-Singha.
Singha.
Fuck, it hurts!
I'm choked up.
Ouch!
Hey.
There's no blood.
Not even a scratch.
You're invulnerable.
Whoa!
What the fuck is that?
Ow, holy shit!
Shit.
Ow, What the fuck?
Now what the hell is that?
These days,
Channel’s getting shallow huh?
Hit the bottom a few times now.
You know?
-Really?
-Yeah.
If the water stays this low,
we won't be able to get the boat in.
Over there.
Gonna have to dock way over.
At Old Man Fin's place.
Fin's boat lane.
Have you even asked him yet?
Why?
The old guy's fine.
But his relative?
-She’s a total pain in the ass.
-Yeah.
Thinks she owns the place.
-Hey, Oil.
-I think I ask...
-What?
-Boat.
What Boat?
A Boat.
Hey, something feels off.
It looks like it's headed straight for our house.
Yeah, it’s heading straight for us.
Hey. Stop!
-Stop!
-Hey! Do you hear me?! It's about to hit!
-Hey, stop. Hey!
-Can't you hear me, dammit!
I said stop.
Hey! It's too late to stop!
Hey.
My wooden pier is completely destroyed!
Go take a look, brother.
-Go look at it now?
-Yeah.
How bad is it?
It's all ruined.
Hey.
Is this a local fisherman's boat?
From one of the docks around here?
We haven't seen this one before either.
We would know it if it were local.
Around what time did the incident occur?
Villagers reported that it might belong to...
Other fishing vessels said that.
They saw this boat just
drifting out there all night long.
The people who saw it said.
Suddenly, an empty boat just
crashed straight into the house.
And the Coast Guard didn't
pick up any distress signals?
No, nothing at all.
Nobody called in anything about this boat.
I have coordinated with
the Department of Fisheries.
To verify the details of this boat.
I've never seen anything like this before.
This smells like murder.
There are bloody talismans
all over the side of the boat.
They were painted by hand with actual blood.
It's some kind of occult
calligraphy or sacred geometry.
Sarge.
Give every corpse a detailed inspection.
Keep looking for more evidence.
Yes.
Damn!
You're really staring a hole through that.
I already put some clothes on her.
Still staring.
Whoa, you're even pursing your lips!
Whoa, you guys are unbelievable.
Why are you nagging so much?
Come on, give us a break
and let us enjoy the view.
Gosh, looking at you is
an eyesore. Makes me want to throw up
But seriously, I think we should call the cops.
Aren't we going to wait for her
to wake up first? Then we can ask.
From the looks of it.
I don't think she's the type
who gets along with the cops.
Singha.
What?
Thought I saw you get shot and fall.
You alright?
No, you idiot. I didn't get hit.
It just grazed me.
It didn't look like a graze to me, though.
Are you sure you're okay?
Hey, search the whole area.
Hey, you! Get over here.
In the last two days,
Have you seen a woman
covered in tattoos around here?
No, I haven't.
Maybe check the bar up there.
Okay, let's go.
Let's get going.
Hey.
Did you guys see a woman covered
in tattoos pass through here last night?
No, we didn't.
And there’s no
woman covered in tattoos around here.
Only this bitch here, and her
tattoos aren't even full body, right?
Let me check inside.
Hey.
-You can't go in. You're not the police!
-Right.
Let him in.
Hey.
Search the whole place.
Damn it, Where is she?
Keep looking, let's go!
Joe.
So, where the fuck did you hide her?
What is this?
Where is she?
-Where to? Go up where?
-Stop complaining.
Where is she hidden?
Hidden right here.
Asshole! How could you leave
her out in the sun like that?
Are you out of your mind?
Hey,
You know.
It was his idea.
Do you think she's sun-dried beef?
Get her down!
She's gonna end up dead.
-Shit, I try to help and I'm still the bad guy.
-Shut up, Joe!
Hurry.
-Toon, look at him.
-You think she's a featherweight?
Who are you and where are you from?
Ooh
Don't tell me you two.
Ooh my ass, I'm just curious.
curious.
Thinking about liking girls too?
You.
That's harsh.
Anyway, I came to say.
The ice truck is here.
You getting ice today?
You opening the shop or what?
Hmm, let's just close for today.
I'll give Singh a call.
Hmm.
Where did Toon go?
Are you gonna call her, or should I?
You do it.
You don't do a damn thing!
Dammit, just go!
-Don't call and you say I'm doing nothing.
-Doing what?
Come in.
Excuse me, sir.
Here’s the preliminary report.
Every single corpse.
Their internal organs are completely rotten.
Toxicology tests found no traces of poison.
And they’ve got some kind of ancient
Khmer symbols written on their foreheads.
Forensics is still looking into it.
Did they say how long they've been dead?
Less than 24 hours.
Just died.
But already rotten inside?
That's right.
The last GPS signal placed the boat.
Was near Koh Larn.
Before reaching Pattaya Beach.
Get me a room.
What?
2,000 per room.
Do you want it.
No interruptions. From anyone.
Bring the whore too.
Yes.
Don't mess with me.
(Khmer prayer)
2,500.
Temporary or overnight?
Temporary.
Uhh...
Do you have
a protector here?
Why? Something wrong?
I don't know.
I think this customer looks...
Creepy in a weird way.
I don't know, it's just off.
If he’s that creepy, then turn him away.
Just tell him we're not accepting
any more guests.
Hey! It's 2,500.
We don't get offers like this often.
Just hire a guard for 300 then.
If nothing happens.
He gets free money.
If there is,
just pay him more.
Send the girl in.
Ok, that's all.
If you need anything.
Just call me.
The money?
2,500.
And another 500 for the girl's ride.
One hour only. No second rounds.
Ouch!
Make sure you guard that room well, alright?
I've got a feeling about this customer.
He’s fucking weird.
Yeah.
Anything happens, I'll blast him open.
Whoa!
Just scare him.
I’m out. Keep an eye on things.
Sir.
Can I cancel?
No.
Just lie down.
What is that?
(Khmer prayer)
Hey! What are you doing?
What are you doing? Let me go!
What are you doing?
Hey! Let me go!
Help!
Help! Someone help me! Get off me!
Hey.
Let the girl go.
or I'll shoot!
You wouldn't dare.
Go ahead and shoot! Do it!
Red-eyed freak.
Using black magic.
Are you insane?
Shoving it in.
Won't make more mystical power.
You sicko!
Bastard!
Think chanting spells
makes you bulletproof, huh?
Move back! Get out of the way!
Hey.
Why did you come out? Get back inside!
Scared the shit out of me.
Hey!
Shit!
What the hell?
Damn
What the fuck?
Ow!
Didn't find?
Go find again.